Guide to the Biographical Reference Collection, 1972-2004 UA.01.11.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Biographical Files
  - Manchester, Alan K. (Box 18)
  - Mann, Glenn Edwin "Ted" [Sports Information] (Box 18)
  - Mann, W. Joseph [Divinity] (Box 18)
  - Manton, Kenneth [Demogarphic Studies] (Box 18)
  - Marchase, Richard B. [Anatomy] (Box 18)
  - Marin, Jack (Box 18)
  - Markham, Sadie Hackney (Box 18)
  - Markman, Sidney D. (Box 18)
  - Marshall, Peter [Chapel Organist] (Box 18)
  - Marshall, Roger (Box 18)
  - Massey, Marilyn Chapin [Religion] (Box 18)
  - Mather, Peter (Box 18)
  - Mathews, Jane De Hart, Ph.D. (Box 18)
  - Matlock, Jack F., Jr. (Box 18)
  - Mauskopf, Seymour [History] (Box 18)
  - Mayer, Robert A. [Longest tenure of a trustee--66 years] (Box 18)
  - Maytubby, Joseph S. (Box 18)
  - McBryde, Angus M. [Original Medical School faculty member] (Box 18)
  - McCarthy, Tara (Box 18)
  - McConahay, John B. (Box 18)
  - McCrary, J. Ray [First member enrolled in 9019] (Box 18)
  - McDermott, Malcolm [Law] (Box 18)
  - McDonald, Eugene J. (Box 18)
  - McDougall, Anne Hickmore (Box 18)
  - McDougall, William (Box 18)
  - McElhaney, James H. (Box 18)
  - McFarland, Leslie (Box 18)
  - McGeachy, Neill [Basketball Coach] (Box 18)
  - McGee, Jerry [Football] (Box 18)
  - McGee, Michael [Football Coach] (Box 18)
  - McGhee, George Crews [Trustee] (Box 18)
  - McGovern, George (Box 18)
  - McGrath, Daniel F. (Box 18)
  - McHugh, Gelolo [Psychology] (Box 18)
  - MacIntyre, Alasdair (Box 18)
  - McAfee, George [Class of 1940. Football--Iron Duke] (Box 18)
  - McKean, Margaret A. [Political Science] (Box 18)
  - McKinney, John C. [Dean, Graduate School] (Box 18)
  - McLean, Edward (Box 18)
  - McLoyd, Vonnie [Psychology] (Box 18)
  - McMahon, J. Alexander (Box 18)
  - McPhail, Andrew T. [Chemistry] (Box 18)
  - Medina, Miguel A. [Civil Engineering] (Box 18)
  - Meier, Otto [Electrical Engineering] (Box 18)
  - Melosh, Robert [Civil Engineering] (Box 18)
  - Menefee, E. E. "Lige," Jr. (Box 18)
  - Meriam, James L. [Engineering] (Box 18)
  - Merkx, Gilbert (Box 18)
  - Merritt, Gertrude E. (Box 18)
  - Meyer, Horst M. [Physics] (Box 18)
  - Meyers, Carol [Religion] (Box 18)
  - Meyers, Edward J. [Library] (Box 18)
  - Meyers, Eric [Religion] (Box 18)
  - Mezzatesta, Michael (Box 18)
  - King Michael of Romania (Box 18)
  - Mickey, Paul [Divinity] (Box 18)
  - Mickiewicz, Ellen [Political Sciences] (Box 18)
  - Miller, Justin [Law] (Box 18)
  - Miller, Martin [History] (Box 18)
  - Mimms, Christine (Box 18)
  - Mims, Edwin (Box 19)
  - Minah, Ted [Director of Dining Halls] (Box 19)
  - Miranda, Marie Lynn [NSOE] (Box 19)
  - Mitchell, Fannie (Box 19)
  - Mogavero, Richard [Drama] (Box 19)
  - Moi, Toril [Literature and Romance Languages] (Box 19)
  - Moneta, Larry [Student Affairs] (Box 19)
  - Monsman, Gerald [English] (Box 19)
  - Monteith, Larry (Box 19)
  - Moore, Julia [Botany] (Box 19)
  - Moore, Kevin (Box 19)
  - Moorman, Claude T. [Director, Sports Medicine Center] (Box 19)
  - Mordecai, Samuel Fox (Box 19)
  - Morelli, Patrick [T 1968] (Box 19)
  - Morey, Richard [Business] (Box 19)
  - Morgan, Henry S. [Bursar] (Box 19)
  - Morrell, E. [Library] (Box 19)
  - Morris, Barbara [Student Health] (Box 19)
  - Moseley, Carlos (Box 19)
  - Moses, Connie (Box 19)
  - Moses, Montrose Jonas (Box 19)
  - Mueller, Earl G. [Art] (Box 19)
  - Mueller, Julia [Music] (Box 19)
  - Mulkey, Hurley (Box 19)
  - Muller, Yvonne (Box 19)
  - Mullins, Jeff [Basketball] (Box 19)
  - Mumford, L. Quincy (Box 19)
  - Murphy, Charles S. (Box 19)
  - Murphy, Evelyn (Box 19)
  - Murphy, Roland E. (Box 19)
  - Murray, Ethel Marsh (Box 19)
  - Murray, Father J-Glenn (Box 19)
  - Murray, Francis J. [Math] (Box 19)
  - Murray, William D. "Bill" [Football] (Box 19)
  - Muskie, Edmund "Ned," Jr. (Box 19)
  - Myers, George C. [Sociology] (Box 19)
  - Nakasone, Yasuhiro (Box 19)
  - Nasher, Raymond (Box 19)
  - Nathans, Sydney [History] (Box 19)
  - Naylor, Aubrey W. [Botany] (Box 19)
  - Naylor, Thomas H. [Economics] (Box 19)
  - Negley, Glenn [Philosophy] (Box 19)
  - Nelson, Ernest (Box 19)
  - Nelson, Larry [University Architect] (Box 19)
  - Nesbit, M. Wilson [Divinity] (Box 19)
  - Nevidjon, Brenda [CEO, Duke Hospital] (Box 19)
  - Neville, Jerry (Box 19)
  - Newbold, Nathan Carter (Box 19)
  - Newman, Anne (Box 19)
  - Newman, Ed [Football] (Box 19)
  - Newsom, Dallas Walton (Box 19)
  - Newson, Henry W. [Physics] (Box 19)
  - Newton, Francis [Classical Studies] (Box 19)
  - Newton, John [Marine Lab] (Box 19)
  - Newton, Suzanne (Box 19)
  - Nicholas, Peter M. [Trustee] (Box 19)
  - Nicholson, William McNeal [Medicine] (Box 19)
  - Neilson, Walter M. [Physics] (Box 19)
  - Niess, Robert J. [Romance Languages] (Box 19)
  - Nijhout, Frederik [Aoology] (Box 19)
  - Nixon, Edward C. (Box 19)
  - Nixon, Nan (Box 19)
  - Nixon, Richard
    - Articles and clippings, pre-1990 (Box 19)
    - Articles and clippings, post-1990 (Box 19)
    - Lengthy articles and other materials (Box 19)
  - Noel, W. Lee [Fuqua] (Box 19)
  - Noren, Carol Marie [Divinity] (Box 19)
  - North, Jeremy [Gothic Bookshop] (Box 19)
  - Novak, Michael (Box 19)
  - Nygard, Holger and Margaret (Box 19)
  - O'Barr, Jean (Box 19)
  - O'Barr,, William [Anthropology] (Box 19)
  - Oates, John F. [Classical Studies] (Box 19)
  - O'Connor, Pat (Box 19)
  - Odell, John M. (Box 19)
  - O'Leary, James J. [Economics] (Box 19)
  - Omang, Joann (Box 19)
  - O'Neal, F. Hodge [Law] (Box 19)
  - Oosting, Henry John [Botany] (Box 19)
  - O'Quinn, Lea (Box 19)
  - Orbach, Michael [Marine Lab] (Box 19)
  - O'Reilly - Terri, Patti, Christine (Box 19)
  - Ormond, Jesse Marvin [Divinity School] (Box 19)
  - Orr, Linda [Romance Languages] (Box 19)
  - Orr, Louis [Duke Etchings] (Box 19)
  - Ortner, Robert (Box 19)
  - Osborn, Robert [Religion] (Box 19)
  - O'Toole, Annette (Box 20)
  - O'Toole, Tim [Basketball] (Box 20)
  - Owens, Ida Stephens [first African-American woman Ph.D., 1967] (Box 20)
  - Page, Walter Hines. Page, Allison. (Box 20)
  - Paletz, David [Political Science] (Box 20)
  - Palmer, Aubrey E. [Engineering] (Box 20)
  - Palmer, Janice (Box 20)
  - Palmer, Michael (Box 20)
  - Palmer, Richard A. [Chemistry] (Box 20)
  - Pardue, Leonard (Box 20)
  - Parker, Clarence "Ace" (Box 20)
  - Parker, Harold T. [History] (Box 20)
  - Parkins, Robert [Organist] (Box 20)
  - Patrick, Ransom R. [Art] (Box 20)
  - Patterson, Eugene C. [Trustee] (Box 20)
  - Patterson, Karl Bachman [Math] (Box 20)
  - Patton, Frances Gray and Lewis (Box 20)
  - Patton, Laurie (Box 20)
  - Payne, Bruce [Policy Sciences] (Box 20)
  - Peach, William [Philosophy] (Box 20)
  - Pearsall, George W. [Engineering] (Box 20)
  - Pearse, A. S. (Arthur Sperry)[Zoology] (Box 20)
  - Peele, Talmage [Medicine] (Box 20)
  - Pegram, William Howell and Annie Pegram (Box 20)
  - Pierce, J. Jeffery (Box 20)
  - Pelech, Orest L. (Box 20)
  - Penfield, Add (Box 20)
  - Perez, Luis Aviles (Box 20)
  - Perkins, Ronald D. [Geology] (Box 20)
  - Perkins, William R. (Box 20)
  - Perry, Harold S. [Botany] (Box 20)
  - Persons, Elizabeth Anderson [Woman's College] (Box 20)
  - Persons, Walter S. "Jack" [Swimming] (Box 20)
  - Petroski, Henry (Box 20)
  - Petry, Ray [Divinity] (Box 20)
  - Phelps, Leland R. [Germanic Languages] (Box 20)
  - Phelps, Stephen F. (Box 20)
  - Phillips, Angus [Fellow in Journalism] (Box 20)
  - Phillips, James H. and Alice (Box 20)
  - Phillips, Paula [Dean, Woman's College] (Box 20)
  - Philpott, Jane (Box 20)
  - Pickens, Marshall I. [Duke Endowment] (Box 20)
  - Picket, Iris [Duke Press] (Box 20)
  - Pickett, J. Phillip (Box 20)
  - Pickrell, Kenneth L. (Box 20)
  - Pietrantoni, Joseph G. (Box 20)
  - Pilkey, Orrin H. [Geology] (Box 20)
  - Pilkington, Theo [Biomedical Engineering] (Box 20)
  - Pinn, Melvin T. [DUMC] (Box 20)
  - Pinsky, Mark (Box 20)
  - Piva, John Jay (Box 20)
  - Plonsey, Robert [Biomedical Engineering] (Box 20)
  - Poirier, Jacques [Chemistry] (Box 20)
  - Poole, Mary Elizabeth [class of 1935] (Box 20)
  - Pope, Deborah [English] (Box 20)
  - Porter, Earl (Box 20)
  - Porter, R. Ross (Box 20)
  - Porter, Joseph A. [English; Writer] (Box 20)
  - Porter, Dr. Ned (Box 20)
  - Portes, Alejandro (Box 20)
  - Postma, Herman (Box 20)
  - Poteat, Mary [English] (Box 20)
  - Poteat, William H. [Divinity] (Box 20)
  - Powell, Benjamin Edward (Box 20)
  - Powell, Richard [Art] (Box 20)
  - Powell, Rufus H, III [Law] (Box 20)
  - Pratt, Edmund T. [Pratt School of Engineering] (Box 20)
  - Pratt, Ella Fountain (Box 20)
  - Pratt, Joseph Gaither [Parapsychology] (Box 20)
  - Pratt, Sheila [Art] (Box 20)
  - Pratt, Vernon [Art] (Box 20)
  - Predmore, Richard L. [Romance Languages] (Box 20)
  - Preiss, Jack Joseph [Sociology] (Box 20)
  - Preston, Richard A. [History] (Box 20)
  - Price, David [Political Science] (Box 20)
  - Price, James L. II (Box 20)
  - Price, Reynolds (Box 21)
    - Awards, symposia, lectures, readings (Box 21)
    - Bibliographies and teaching (Box 21)
    - Biographical: 1960s-2000s [4 folders] (Box 21)
    - Book and play reviews (Box 21)
    - Writings, addresses, etc. (Box 21)
  - Proctor, Arthur Marcus (Box 21)
  - Putman, Charles E. (Box 21)
  - Pyatt, Timothy D. [2nd Duke University Archivist] (2 folders) (Box 21)
  - Pye, A. Kenneth [Law; Administration] (Box 21)
  - Quick, William K. (Box 21)
  - Quin, Louis D. [Chemistry] (Box 21)
  - Raimi, Fred [Music] (Box 21)
  - Rainey, Harry "Uncle Harry" (Box 21)
  - Ralston, C. W. [Forestry] (Box 21)
  - Ramm, Dietolf [Computer Science] (Box 21)
  - Ramus, Joseph [Botany] (Box 21)
  - Randall, Dale [English; Drama] (Box 21)
  - Randolph-Wright, Charles (Box 21)
  - Rankin, Dorothy Newsom (Box 21)
  - Rankin, Robert S. [Political Science] (Box 21)
  - Rankin, Tom [Center for Documentary Studies] (Box 21)
  - Rankin, W. W. [Mathematics] (Box 21)
  - Raspberry, William [Terry Sanford Institute of Public Policy] (Box 21)
  - Ratchford, Benjamin U. [Economics] (Box 21)
  - Raymond, Mary Lois [Romance Languages] (Box 21)
  - Reagan, Ronald [President] (Box 21)
  - Reardon, Kenneth [English; Drama] (Box 21)
  - Reckhow, Kenneth H. [Forestry; Environmental Science] (Box 21)
  - Reddy, William M. [History] (Box 21)
  - Reeve, Catherine [Parking and Transportation] (Box 21)
  - Reichenberg-Hackett, Wally [Psychology] (Box 21)
  - Rennie, John [Soccer Coach] (Box 21)
  - Reppy, William A., Jr. [Law] (Box 21)
  - Reynolds, Jacqueline [Biochemistry] (Box 21)
  - Rhine, Louisa [Parapsychology] (Box 21)
  - Rhine, J. B. [Parapsychology] (Box 21)
  - Rhyne, Charles [Law] (Box 21)
  - Richards, John F. (Box 21)
  - Richardson, Curtis [Forestry; Environmental Studies] (Box 21)
  - Richardson, Lawrence, Jr. [Classical Studies] (Box 21)
  - Richardson, Robert C. [Ph.D 1966; Trustee; Nobel] (Box 21)
  - Richey, McMurry S. [Divinity School] (Box 22)
  - Richey, Russell [Divinity School] (Box 22)
  - Richmond, Harold Perry [Mechanical Engineering] (Box 22)
  - Riebel, John [Physical Education] (Box 22)
  - Riddell, Richard [Drama Department] (Box 22)
  - Riedel, Eberhard [Physics] (Box 22)
  - Riggsbee, Jan J. [Education] (Box 22)
  - Rigsby, Kent [Classical Studies] (Box 22)
  - Ripley, Dana [French] (Box 22)
  - Ritchie, B. Maurice [Divinity School] (Box 22)
  - Roberson, N. Russell [Physics] (Box 22)
  - Robert, Joseph C. [History] (Box 22)
  - Roberts, Darryl L. [Political Science] (Box 22)
  - Roberts, Verne [Mechanical Engineering] (Box 22)
  - Robinson, Charles [Divinity School] (Box 22)
  - Robinson, Hugh C. [Physics] (Box 22)
  - Robinson, Roscoe R. [DUMC] (Box 22)
  - Robinson, Russell (Box 22)
  - Robinson, Tanya (Box 22)
  - Rogers, Annie [Housekeeping] (Box 22)
  - Rogers, Robert Samuel [Classical Studies] (Box 22)
  - Rojstaczer, Stuart [NSOE] (Box 22)
  - Roland, Alex [History] (Box 22)
  - Rolleston, James L. [Germanic Languages] (Box 22)
  - Roney family (includes genealogical info) (Box 22)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore. [Visit, 1905] (Box 22)
  - Roper, Daniel C. [Trustee] (Box 22)
  - Ropp, Theodore "Ted" [History] (Box 22)
  - Rose, Charlie (Box 22)
  - Rose, Jed E. (Box 22)
  - Rosendahl, Bruce [Geologist] (Box 22)
  - Roses, Allen [Neurologist] (Box 22)
  - Ross, Susan Cranford (Box 22)
  - Rossiter, Al, Jr. (Box 22)
  - Rothschild, Mauro Jeffery (Box 22)
  - Rowe, Gilbert T. [Religion/Divinity] (Box 22)
  - Rowe, Thomas D., Jr. (Box 22)
  - Rowson, Richard [Director, Duke Press] (Box 22)
  - Roy, Donald [Sociology] (Box 22)
  - Ruderman, Judith (Box 22)
  - Ruden, John J. [Divinity School] (Box 22)
  - Ruffin, Julian M. [DUMC] (Box 22)
  - Rundles, R. Wayne (Box 22)
  - Rush, Kenneth [Law] (Box 22)
  - Russell, Elbert [Divinity School] (Box 22)
  - Russell, Mattie (Box 22)
  - Ryals, Clyde de L. (Box 22)
  - Sabiston, David Coston, Jr. (Box 22)
  - Saito, Vicki Y. (Box 22)
  - Salamon, Lester, M. [Political Science] (Box 22)
  - Salinger, Herman and Marion (Box 22)
  - Salazano, John Victor [Physiology] (Box 22)
  - Sanders, C. Richard [English] (Box 22)
  - Sandeen, Muriel I. [Zoology] (Box 22)
  - Sands, Alexander H., Jr. [Trustee] (Box 22)
  - Sanford, David H. [Philosophy] (Box 22)
  - Sanford, Margaret Rose (Box 22)
  - Sanford, Terry
    - Articles, 1960-1979 – Oversize newspaper – MC_30 (Box 22)
    - Articles, 1980-1989 (Box 22)
    - Articles, 1990- (Box 22)
    - Funeral and remembrances, April 21, 1998- (Box 22)
    - Remembrances and news articles, April 19-22, 1998 (Box 22)
  - Satterfield, Peggy Jane Warren (Box 22)
  - Saville, Lloyd B. [Economics] and Eugenia [Music] (Box 22)
  - Sawyer, Otis G. (Box 22)
  - Sawyer, Robert N. [Education; Talent Identification Program] (Box 22)
  - Saylor, John H. (Box 22)
  - Schaefer, Norb F. "Bud," Jr. (Box 22)
  - Schauf, Cam (Box 22)
  - Schewel, Steve [The Independent] (Box 22)
  - Schlesinger, William H. [Dean, NSOE] (Box 22)
  - Schlitz, Don [Songwriter, known for "The Gambler"] (Box 22)
  - Schmid, Ron (Box 22)
  - Schmidt-Nielsen, Knut (Box 22)
  - Schock, Carl (Box 22)
  - Schoenfeld, Michael J. [Vice President for Public Affairs and Government Relations] (Box 22)
  - Schroeder, Christopher H. [Law] (Box 22)
  - Schroeder, Richard A. (Box 22)
  - Schumacher, Francis Xavier (Box 22)
  - Schumann, Marguerite E. [Author, Stones, Bricks & Faces] (Box 22)
  - Schweitzer, Georgia [Women's Basketball] (Box 23)
  - Sclafani, Matthew A. [Chronicle] (Box 23)
  - Scott, Anne [History] (Box 23)
  - Scott, Ernest Findlay [Divinity School] (Box 23)
  - Scott, Jean [History; Admissions] (Box 23)
  - Seale, William (Box 23)
  - Searles, Richard [Botany] (Box 23)
  - Sears, Amy [Young Trustee] (Box 23)
  - Seaver, Donald M. (Box 23)
  - Sedgwick, Eve Kosofsky [English] (Box 23)
  - Seebass, Talman [Music] (Box 23)
  - Seeley, Walter J. [Electrical Engineering] (Box 23)
  - Seeman, Ernest (Box 23)
  - Sefton, Norman (Box 23)
  - Segrest, Mab (Box 23)
  - Semans Family Photos. Inventory (Box 23)
  - Semans, James Hustead (Box 23)
  - Semans, Mary Duke Biddle Trent
    - Awards and honors (Box 23)
    - Biographical (Box 23)
    - Christmas cards (Box 23)
    - Speeches and letters (Box 23)
  - Semans, Truman Thomas, Jr. "Tommy" (Box 23)
  - Serafin, Donald [Surgery] (Box 23)
  - Shabel, Fred (Box 23)
  - Shands, Alfred R. (Box 23)
  - Shankle, Joel and Mike (Box 23)
  - Shapiro, Michael [Art] (Box 23)
  - Sharon, Boaz (Box 23)
  - Sharpe, John L, III (Box 23)
  - Shaughnessy, Edward J. [Mechanical Engineering] (Box 23)
  - Shaw, Barbara Ramsay [Chemistry] (Box 23)
  - Schears, Randolph Moore "Nurmi" (Box 23)
  - Sheffield, William M. (Box 23)
  - Shepherd, Howard Bruce (Box 23)
  - Shepherd, Robert S. [University Development] (Box 23)
  - Sheppard, Blair (Box 23)
  - Sherwin, Leonard (Box 23)
  - Shimm, Melvin [Law] (Box 23)
  - Shingleton, William (Box 23)
  - Shockley, Grant [Divinity School] (Box 23)
  - Shuman, R. Baird [Education] (Box 23)
  - Shumate, David [Sponsored Programs] (Box 23)
  - Shytle, John D. [Medical Center] (Box 23)
  - Siedow, James [Botany] (Box 23)
  - Siegel, Lewis M. (Box 23)
  - Siemer, Richard P. [Vice president for administrarion] (Box 23)
  - Sigler, Joe (Box 23)
  - Silar, Jackie [Assistant Athletic Director] (Box 23)
  - Silberman, Bernard S. [Far Eastern history] (Box 23)
  - Silberman, Harold [Medicine] (Box 23)
  - Silver, Brian (Box 23)
  - Silver, Donald [DUMC] (Box 23)
  - Sime, Dave (Box 23)
  - Simmons, Ervin (Box 23)
  - Simmons, Funiford M. [Senator] (Box 23)
  - Simons, Elwyn, L. [Primates] (Box 23)
  - Simpson, William "Suitcase" [Political Science] (Box 23)
  - Sindler, Allan P. (Box 23)
  - Sirica, John J., Jr. (Box 23)
  - Sirikit, Queen of Thailand, visit Feb 1980 (Box 23)
  - Skarulis, Patricia (Box 23)
  - Slaughter, Enos [Baseball Coach] (Box 23)
  - Slaughter, Frank G. (Box 23)
  - Sloan, Steve [Head Coach, Football] (Box 23)
  - Small, Margaret "Bunny" (Box 23)
  - Smeal, Eleanor Cutre (Box 23)
  - Smith, James Benjamin, Jr. "Ben" [Director, Chapel Choir, 1968 - 1988] (Box 23)
  - Smith, D. Moody [Divinity School] (Box 23)
  - Smith, David T. [Microbiology] (Box 23)
  - Smith, Grover (Box 23)
  - Smith, H. Shelton [Divinity School] (Box 23)
  - Smith, Harmon L. [Divinity School. Theology] (Box 23)
  - Smith, Joel [Sociology] (Box 23)
  - Smith, Kathleen (Box 23)
  - Smith, Larry [Baseball] (Box 23)
  - Smith, Margaret Taylor (Box 23)
  - Smith, Robert Sidney [Economics] (Box 23)
  - Smith, Ruth Slack (Box 23)
  - Smith, Susan Carlton (Box 23)
  - Smith, William Kennedy (Box 23)
  - Smullin, Frank (Box 24)
  - Sneed, Joseph T. [Law] (Box 24)
  - Snyderman, Ralph (Box 24)
  - Soenksen, Gordon D. (Box 24)
  - Solie, Guy (Box 24)
  - Soong, Charles J. (Box 24)
  - Soper, Edmund Davison [School of Religion] (Box 24)
  - Souchak, Mike (Box 24)
  - Southern, Edwin (Box 24)
  - Southgate, James Haywood (Box 24)
  - Spanarkel, Jim [Basketball] (Box 24)
  - Sparks, Thad (Box 24)
  - Spaulding, Jean [Psychiatry; Trustee] (Box 24)
  - Speakes, Ruben Lee (Box 24)
  - Spears, Estelle Flowers (Box 24)
  - Spence, Hersey Everett [Divinity School] (Box 24)
  - Spencer, John R. [Art] (Box 24)
  - Spengler, Joseph J. and Dorothy K. (Box 24)
  - Sponer, Hertha [Physics], and James Franck (Box 24)
  - Spragens, Tom (Box 24)
  - Springer, Roxanne [Physics] (Box 24)
  - Spurrier, Steve (Box 24)
  - Stachitas, Leonard P. (Box 24)
  - Stack, Carol [Anthropology] (Box 24)
  - Staddon, John [Psychology] (Box 24)
  - Staelin, Richard (Box 24)
  - Stainback, J. Preston (Box 24)
  - Stairs, Gerald (Box 24)
  - Stambaugh, William [Plant Pathology; American Chestnut research] (Box 24)
  - Stambaugh-Worthington, Amy (Box 24)
  - Stanbury, Walter Albert (Box 24)
  - Stansbury, Dale F. (Box 24)
  - Stanley, Keith [Classical Studies] (Box 24)
  - Stark, Lori [Field Hockey] (Box 24)
  - Starnes, Hugh L. [Dining Halls] (Box 24)
  - Starnes, Marian [Bursar] (Box 24)
  - Starr, Kenneth W. [Judge; U. S. Solicitor General] (Box 24)
  - Stars, William K. [Art Department; Art Museum] (Box 24)
  - Stead, Eugene A., Jr. (Box 24)
  - Steckley, Linda G. [Law] (Box 24)
  - Steele, Richard E. [Admissions] (Box 24)
  - Steffak, Ed [See: Duke Gardens Collection] (Box 24)
  - Steinmetz, David C. [Divinity School] (Box 24)
  - Stern, Louis William (Box 24)
  - Stevenson, Lionel [English] (Box 24)
  - Stewart, Carl J., Jr. (Box 24)
  - Stewart, Philip [Romance Languages] (Box 24)
  - Stinespring, William F. (Box 24)
  - Stolz, Otto [Law] (Box 24)
  - Stone, Donald E. (Box 24)
  - Stone, Mabel U. [Alumni Affairs] (Box 24)
  - Storer, Jeffrey (Box 24)
  - Stoughton, W. Vickery [Vice Chancellor and CEO, DUMC] (Box 24)
  - Strain, Boyd [Botany] (Box 24)
  - Strandberg, Victor [English] (Box 24)
  - Strange, John Hadley [Political Science] (Box 24)
  - Strobel, Howard [Chemistry] (Box 24)
  - Strohbehn, John W. [Provost] (Box 24)
  - Strome, Steve [Tennis Coach] (Box 24)
  - Strowd, Elvin (Box 24)
  - Struhsaker, Thomas [Biological Anthropology and Anatomy] (Box 24)
  - Stubbing, Richard A. [Administration] (Box 24)
  - Stumpf, Whippert Arnot [Education] (Box 24)
  - Styron, William (Box 24)
  - Sunderland, Elizabeth [Art] (Box 25)
  - Surwit, Richard [Medical Psychology] (Box 25)
  - Swanson, Louis Earl (Box 25)
  - Swett, Elizabeth (Box 25)
  - Sydnor, Charles S. (Box 25)
  - Taliaferro, Clay [Dance] (Box 25)
  - Tanford, Charles [Biochemistry] (Box 25)
  - Taube, Mortimer [Library] (Box 25)
  - Taylor, Mabel [Dope Shop] (Box 25)
  - Taylor, Michael William (Box 25)
  - Teer, Nello Leguy (Box 25)
  - TePaske John T. [History] (Box 25)
  - Terborgh, John (Box 25)
  - Tetel, Marcel (Box 25)
  - Thaler, Roger (Box 25)
  - Thibodeau, Patricia L. [Duke Medical Center Library] (Box 25)
  - Thomas, James A. (Box 25)
  - Thomas, Joseph M. [Mathematics] (Box 25)
  - Thomas, R. David (Box 25)
  - Thompson, Anne S. (Box 25)
  - Thompson, Edgar T. [Sociology] (Box 25)
  - Thompson, Robert (Box 25)
  - Thurston, Frederick [Biomedical Engineering] (Box 25)
  - Tifft, Susan (Box 25)
  - Tilley, Nannie May (Box 25)
  - Tipton, Eric (Box 25)
  - Tirro, Frank P. [Music] (Box 25)
  - Tiryakian, Edward H. [Sociology] (Box 25)
  - Tischendorf, Alfred Paul [History] (Box 25)
  - Tisdale, Wright [Trustee] (Box 25)
  - Tjoflat, Gerald Bard [Chief Judge] (Box 25)
  - Tobias, Randall [Trustee] (Box 25)
  - Todd, R. Larry [Music] (Box 25)
  - Tompkins, Jane [Engllish] (Box 25)
  - Toms, Clinton White (Box 25)
  - Towe, Kenneth Crawford (Box 25)
  - Trask, Tallman, III [Administration] (Box 25)
  - Treml, Vladimir [Economics] (Box 25)
  - Trent, Josiah Charles (Box 25)
  - Trickey, Philip H. [Electrical Engineering] (Box 25)
  - Trudeau, Pierre [Canadian Prime Minister] (Box 25)
  - Trusdale, James N. [Classical Studies] (Box 25)
  - Trumbauer, Horace (Box 25)
  - Tsui, Anne S. [Fuqua] (Box 25)
  - Tucker, Gene [Divinity School] (Box 25)
  - Tucker, Vance [Zoology] (Box 25)
  - Turner, Arlin [English] (Box 25)
  - Turner, William C. [Divinity School] (Box 25)
  - Tuthill, R. L. [Geology] (Box 25)
  - Tutu, Bishop Desmond [Republic of South Africa] (Box 25)
  - Tyler, Anne (Box 25)
  - Tyree, William Allen (Box 25)
  - Tyson, Tim (Box 25)
  - Upchurch, W. M. (Box 25)
  - Urguidi, Victor L. [President, El Colegio de Mexico] (Box 25)
  - Vacendak, Steve (Box 25)
  - Vail, Charles R. [Electrical Engineering] (Box 25)
  - Van Alstyne, William [Law] (Box 25)
  - Vander Weide, James H. [Finance] (Box 25)
  - Vaupel, James W. (Box 25)
  - Vesic, Aleksandar S. [Engineering] (Box 25)
  - Vesilind, P. Aarne [Civil Engineering] (Box 25)
  - Vick, Lois [English] (Box 25)
  - Vick, Paul [Administration] (Box 25)
  - Vieux, Hardy [ASDU President] (Box 25)
  - Vincent, Marjorie (Box 25)
  - Vogel, Steven [Zoology] (Box 25)
  - Viscusi, W. Kip (Box 25)
  - Vollmer, Clement [Germanic Languages and Literature] (Box 25)
  - Vollmer, Maude (Box 25)
  - Volpp, Louis D. [Department of Business Administration] (Box 25)
  - Von Beckerath, Dr. Herbert (Box 25)
  - Von Nardoff, Elfrida (Box 25)
  - Vosburgh, Warren C. [Chemistry] (Box 25)
  - Wackerman, Albert (Box 25)
  - Wade, Charles B., Jr. (Box 25)
  - Wade, Wallace [Football] (2 folders) (Box 26)
  - Wagoner, G. Richard, Jr. (Box 26)
  - Waggoner, John P. "Jake" (Box 26)
  - Wainwright, Geoffrey [Divinity School] (Box 26)
  - Walker, William D. [Physics] (Box 26)
  - Wall, Art, Jr. (Box 26)
  - Wall, George Frank (Box 26)
  - Wallace, Andrew G. [DUMC] (Box 26)
  - Wallace, Harold Gene (Box 26)
  - Wallace, Max (Box 26)
  - Wallace, Randall [Novelist] (Box 26)
  - Wallace, T. Dudley [Economics] (Box 26)
  - Wallach, Michael and Lise [Psychology] (Box 26)
  - Walter, Richard L. [Physics] (Box 26)
  - Walton, Loring B. [Romance Languages] (Box 26)
  - Wannamaker, William Hane (Box 26)
  - Ward, Benjamin [Assistant Dean of Residential Life] (Box 26)
  - Ward, Calvin L. [Zoology] (Box 26)